moreover.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy | Moreover Technologies

###  **Moreover Technologies, Inc. Privacy Policy**

####  Thank you for visiting www.moreover.com (the “ **Website** ”). We value and respect your privacy, and this privacy policy (the “ **Privacy Policy** ”) is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use, and protect any information you may provide to us. Our Terms of Use available at [http://moreover.com/terms-and-conditions] describe the terms and conditions governing your access to and use of the Website and are incorporated herein by reference and form an essential part of the Privacy Policy. **Your use of the Website, and continued use of the Website following any changes to the Privacy Policy, signifies your consent to be legally bound by both the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy and those set forth in our Terms of Use. If you do not agree to the terms of the Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website or provide any information to us.**

#####  The Information We Collect

In order to use the Website to license certain types of content or services or to otherwise submit comments, interact with other users, and/or payment information, you will need to create an account. To set up an account, we collect certain personally identifiable information (“ **Personal Information** ”), as set forth, below. We may also collect certain indirect and/or aggregate information as a result of your use of, and interaction with, the Website (“ **Usage Information** ”).

#####  PERSONAL INFORMATION

When you create your account, we may ask you to provide Personal Information, which may include but is not limited to your:

  * name
  * e-mail address

You may choose not to provide your Personal Information; however creating an account is a prerequisite for using the full functions of the Website.

#####  USAGE INFORMATION

We may also utilize certain standard web measurement and tracking technologies such as “cookies,” web server logs, or other statistics programs to collect Usage Information and track and record how you use the Website. This data is anonymous and does not personally identify you. Usage Information helps us measure the success of the Website and its features or pages and to improve your online experience. Your browser may have an option that allows you to accept cookies, reject cookies, or receive notification when a cookie is sent, but you should note that the use of such restrictive browser settings may limit your use of the Website. In addition, we may utilize beaconing technologies (also known as "action tags" or "one pixel .gif files"), provided by Moreover and/or publishing partners, to measure the effectiveness of, and otherwise manage distribution and/or content offerings. These beacons enable our server and/or publishing partners to recognize the content you access when you visit the Website and to determine the origination site of users arriving at the Website. We do not use spy ware, adware or any other similarly intrusive software.

#####  USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

We use your information in order to provide the services you request and to analyze, manage and improve the Website so that we may continually strive to provide you with the best possible solution. In compliance with applicable laws, it is our policy to require only the Personal Information necessary to enable use to complete the specific transaction that you request; we do not condition your participation in any specific activity on our Website, including any transaction, on the disclosure of more Personal Information than is reasonably necessary to complete such that specific activity and/or transaction. Information such as traffic patterns and the number of page visits helps us to further develop and improve the Website layout to better meet your needs. We also use information such as your name and e-mail address to contact you, respond to your inquiries, and send you information. We may use such information to notify you of special offers and other services that we believe may be of interest to you or to notify you of important new changes to the Website. Finally, we use collected information to help us diagnose problems with our server or other technical issues relating to the performance of the Website. You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., name, email address, personal photographs) on a bulletin board, chat room or on any other community forum offered on the Website, such information may be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other parties. We have no control over this type use of your personally identifiable information and, as such, are not responsible for its use or misuse.

#####  DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may disclose the information we collect from and about you including Usage Information: (a) when we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, customers or other users of the Website, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities, or is appropriate or necessary to enforce the Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, investigate and defend against any third-party claims or allegations, and/or protect the security or integrity of the Website; (b) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws; (c) to our business partners for research, analytical and marketing purposes, such as analyzing usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Website and/or to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf or on behalf of our business partners who may provide such Personal Information in conjunction with its corporate account; or (d) otherwise with your consent. We may sell or buy other businesses or entities. In such event, we may transfer or assign the information we have collected as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In such transactions, your Personal Information may be included in the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used and your Personal Information may be included in the transferred assets. We may use your Usage Information and share it with certain third parties to identify and develop products and services that may be of interest to you and certain demographic groups. We do not sell your Personal Information, to third parties and have no intention of doing so in the future. Under the laws of some jurisdictions, you may be entitled to request disclosure regarding how we share your Usage Information with third parties for direct marketing purposes (“ **Information-Sharing Disclosure** ”). To the extent required by applicable law, we shall provide the Information-Sharing Disclosure to you upon rightful request made in writing to Moreover Technologies, Inc., 1902 Campus Commons Drive Suite 400, Reston, VA 20191-1563. Except as explained above, we will not share any of your Personal Information with any third party, unless we have received your express permission to do so.

#####  OPTING-OUT

You may opt-out of receiving communications about special offers or programs by clicking on a link provided at the bottom of the email communication. 

#####  U.S.-EU and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Compliance

Moreover Technologies complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland.  Moreover Technologies has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.  To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Moreover Technologies certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

In compliance with the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles, we commit to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection, use, or retention of your personal information.  Those with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact us by email, phone or letter at:

  * Email: legal [at] moreover [dot] com

  * Mail: **Worldwide HQ**  
Moreover Technologies, Inc.  
1902 Campus Commons Drive, Suite 400,  
Reston, VA 20191-1563  
Tel:+1 937 485 2906   (select menu  item 2 for customer support)

**              or**

  * **London, UK**  
Moreover Technologies, Ltd.  
69 Turnmill Street  
London  
EC1M 5RR  
Tel: +44 (0)207 253 5003  

We have further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles to an independent recourse mechanism.  If you do not receive timely acknowledgement of your complaint, or if we do not address your complaint to your satisfaction, the matter will be referred to JAMS.  To submit a case, please go to: <http://www.jamsadr.com/contactus/fbGeneral.aspx?xpST=submitaCase>

#####  LINKED SITES

Our Website may contain links to other websites (such as those of our publishing partners or advertisers), which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the collection, use or disclosure of information collected through third-party websites and expressly disclaims any liability related to such collection, use or disclosure. We are also not responsible for any information or content contained on such websites. Links to other websites are provided solely as a convenience. Your browsing, use and interaction on any other websites, including websites which have a link to the Website, are subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Accordingly, we recommend that you review the privacy policy posted on any website that you may access through, or which links to the Website

#####  CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

The Website is not directed to, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from, children under the age of 13. We recommend that parents actively participate in their children’s use of the Internet. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not use or access the Website at any time or in any manner. If you believe that you may have information regarding a person under 13 that you believe to have registered an account with, or otherwise provided Personal Information via, the Website, please contact us at legal [at] moreover [dot] com.

#####  SECURITY PROCEDURES

We take commercially reasonable precautions and have implemented commercially reasonable technical measures intended to protect against the risks of unauthorized access to, erroneous disclosure of, and unlawful interception of Personal Information submitted via the Website. However, your email transmissions and/or other communications containing Personal Information may be unlawfully intercepted or accessed by third parties and/or the Website may be subject to hostile network attacks or administrative errors. We cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information transmitted over the Internet. Once we receive your Personal Information, we take steps that we believe are commercially reasonable to limit access to your Personal Information to only those employees and service providers whom we determine need access to the Personal Information to provide the requested products, services, offers or opportunities that may be of interest to you. However, even after we receive your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee that your Personal Information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed as a result of a breach of our commercially reasonable efforts or as a result of any other event beyond our reasonable control. Accordingly, we cannot and do not guarantee that your Personal Information is completely secure and safe from such risks. **For the avoidance of doubt, WE expressly disclaim any representation or warranty, whether express or implied, with respect to ensuring, guaranteeing or otherwise offering any definitive promise of security in connection with your PERSONAL Information or Usage Information.**

#####  SPECIAL NOTE TO INTERNATIONAL USERS

By using the Website, you agree and acknowledge that the Website is hosted in the United States. If you are attempting to access the Website from a physical location within the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Website, which is governed by U.S. law, the Privacy Notice, and the Terms of Use, you are transferring your Personal Information to the United States and you consent to (i)such transfer, (ii) the application of the laws of the United States and/or the State of Virginia with respect to any dispute arising from or related to the Privacy Policy and/or your use of the Website, other than such rules, regulations, case law, and/or international treaties that would result in the application of the laws of a jurisdiction other than the United States or the State of Virginia, and (iii) the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the United States or the State of Virginia. Any claim or dispute between you and us that arises in whole or in part from your use of the Website or in connection with the Privacy Policy shall be decided exclusively by a court of competent jurisdiction located in the State of Virginia, U.S.A. Each party hereby agrees that such court shall have _in personam_ jurisdiction and venue with respect to such party, and each party hereby submits to the _in personam_ jurisdiction and venue of such courts and waives any objection based on inconvenient forum.

#####  CHANGES AND UPDATES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

From time to time, we may revise the Privacy Policy. To help you stay current of any changes, we take the following two steps: (1) we note the date the Privacy Policy was last updated below (2) when we make a change to the Privacy Policy, we post conspicuous announcement of such changes on the homepage of the Website for 30 days following the date the Privacy Policy was updated. Your use of the Website following the posting of any revised Privacy Policy shall be deemed acceptance of the revised policy, so we strongly recommend that you check back the Privacy Policy periodically. If, and only if, we make revisions to the Privacy Policy that result in a material lessening of the restrictions on our use or disclosure of your Personal Information, we will make a commercially reasonable attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such Personal Information.

If you disagree with the terms of any Privacy Policy at any time, your sole remedy is to terminate your use of the Website and inform us of such termination as described in Privacy Policy. Continued use of the Website constitutes your agreement to any Privacy Policy, as in effect.

#####  CONTACT INFORMATION:

If you have any questions or comments with respect to the Privacy Policy, your rights hereunder, or your opt-in or opt-out choices, please contact us at legal [at] moreover [dot] com.

#####  MISCELLANEOUS:

If any part of the Privacy Policy is determined to be invalid or unenforceable pursuant to applicable law, then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that most closely matches the intent of the original provision and the remainder of the Privacy Policy shall continue in force and effect.

_Last revised: 5/6/2013_
